A Guide to the Papers of Edythe C. Harrison 1961-1993
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Campaign Files
  - Campaign for the United States Senate 1984
    - Virginia Legislative Directory 1984 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Letters to Virginia Leaders announcing Edie's candidacy for the Senate (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Edie Letters to the Editor (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Letters: Dear Friend Letters re: Edies's Candidacy 1984 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Letter: To Delegates March 19, 1984 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 7)
    - JKBG Letter File/Edie Harrison (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Marathon Schedule (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous: Virginia Press List (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Pre-Convention Mailings (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Leadership Mailing Update from Rick Ridder September 1984 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Map-Tidewater (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Television and Radio Buy Made (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Edie Make-Up (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Harrison Memo to Supporters (July) (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 16)
    - METRO-Application (permit to canvass) Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Mondale-Ferraro (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 18)
    - NAACP State Convention Program (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 19)
    - NAIW National Association of Insurance Woman (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 20)
    - NARFE Debate-Arrangments (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 21)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 22)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) Leadership list and letters 1983-84 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 23)
    - National Women Education Fund (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 24)
    - National Women's Political Caucus (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 25)
    - NWPC Senate Voting Record (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Edie '84: Senate Campaign Materials 1984 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Network-NWPC-NOW contract for lists of ERA supporters (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Harrison Network (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Nusbaum Letterhead (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Organization for Rehabilitation through Training (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Phone Bank Scripts (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Poll: Cambridge Survey Research (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Poll: Welsh Memo on Day's Poll (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Poll: Peter Hart (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Portrait Photo-Edie Harrison (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Democratic National Committee-Poll Voter Attitudes 1976 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Press (Raw Info) (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 12)
    - National Directory of Periodicals (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Call for Primary (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Prospectus for Victory (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 15)
    - American Federation of Home Health Agencies-questionnaire response (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Concerned Citizens for Christian Goverment-questionnaire (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Common Cause Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Questionnaires Answered (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Unanswered Questionnaires (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Do Not Answer-Questionnaires (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax Chamber-Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Freeze-Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 3)
    - League of Women Voters-Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 9th Congressional District-Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Relators-Questionnaire Response August 31, 1984 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 6)
    - NARFE (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Taxpayers Association-Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Ridder Campaign Plan September 6, 1984 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Reimbursment Forms (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Republicans (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Resources (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Safire article (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Services and Vendors Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Surrogate Speakers Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Senate Campaign July-December 1983 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Staff List (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 17)
    - State Board of Elections (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Support Enforcement (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Thank You Notes from Edie (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Non-Money Thnak You Notes (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Dorothy Troubetzkoy (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 22)
    - United States Senate-financial disclosure notice (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Beach Mock Election October 22, 1984 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Congressional District Maps (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Conservative Education and Research Institute (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Federate of Democratic Women's Clubs (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Election Returns by County 1980 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Virginia State Legislators List (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Voter Registration (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Edie's Voting Record Ratings (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Edie's Voting Record Research (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Volunteer Identification Forms (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Voting Registration 1984 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Vivian Watts (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Bobby Watson (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 36)
    - J. Harvie Wilkinson III (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Women's Campaign Research Fund-Study of Women Candidates and Fundraising 1984 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 38)
    - W.P. Files-Wang Index (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Women and the 1984 Elections (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Women's Vote Project (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Davis Contributors-alphabetical order last name 1982 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Davis Contributors 1982 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Davis Contributors Congressional District 8 and 10 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dick Davis-Senate Fundrasing Plan 1982 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Lists: Democratic Party whole state (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 7)
    - D.C. Area List (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 8)
    - D.C. Area Women's Equity Action List League Members (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Northern Virginia Jewish Mailing List (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Northern Virginia Rose Thurman Lists (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Northern Virginia B'nai B'rith (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Virginia-National Organization of Women Members 1983 (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Planned Parenthood phone tree (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Prospects-Tidewater Hampton Roads (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 15)
    - List: National Women's Organization (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Previous Contributors-Harrison (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Robb-Bailes List of Contributors (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Soviet Jewry Program Tidewater (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Vivian Watts List-Women's Issues (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Women's Network-Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Ted-Federal Election Commission Report of Contributing PACs (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Women's Equity Action League of Virginia (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 3)
    - California Fund Raising (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Chicago July, 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Detroit Area (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Machinists Dinner-Roanoke (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Northern Virginia Fund Raising-Chapman Event (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Linkhart Event-New York City (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Women's National Democratic Club (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Northern Virginia Events-WPC, Flannery, Women's Democratic Club (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk Money-Campaign Meeting (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Women's Political Caucus Event-Wells Theater, Norfolk September 15, 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Fund-raiser, Edie and Governor Robb-Virginia Beach October 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fund-raiser, Birthday Parties 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Sample Birthday Party Kit (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Fund-raiser Norfolk, VA guest: Gary Hart October 9, 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Fundraising Events (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jerry Adams (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 20)
    - California-Letters Sent (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Davis and Baliles Letters for Edie October 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Diamonstein/Deomcratic Party fundraising letter for Harrison (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Harrison D.C. Contributors (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Fundraising List #1-Sent November, 1983 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Fundraising Letters Sent-individual copies (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Responses to Fundraising Letters June 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Harrison Direct Mail-post September 1, 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jewish Letter Sent to Tidewater, Richmond, Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Fundraising letters by Joan (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Metzenbaum Letter (direct mail) (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Draft Jewish Fundraising Letter (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Finance draft fundraising letters (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Gloria Steinem Fundraising letter (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Fundraising Contacts-Calls to Make (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Mailgrams (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising Phone Calls (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising Calls-Generic List (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Democratic National Committee Political Action Committee List (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee PAC List (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 8)
    - DNC PAC List 1984 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Political Action Committee Information (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Political Action Committees (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 11)
    - AFGE-PAC Application (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Labor PAC labels (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Women Political Action Committee (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO questionnaire (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 16)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Amalagated Transit Union (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Bakery, Confectionery and Tabacco Worker's Union (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Communication Workers of America (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Stewart Rawlings Mott and Kappy Jo Wells (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 21)
    - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 22)
    - NAT-PAC (pro-Israel) (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 23)
    - NARFE (National Association of Retired Federal Employees) (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Virginia N.O.W.-PAC (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 25)
    - National Women's Political Caucus application (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Realtors-PAC (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Senior Political Action Committee (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Letter from Edie to Dennis Kivikko, UFCW (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 29)
    - USATCO (United States Air Traffic Controllers Organization) (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Education Association questionnaire (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Education Association (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Organization to Keep Abortion Legal (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Political Action Commmittees-Harrison Contributors (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Finance Sample letter to Jewish PACS (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 2)
    - PAC mailings September 11, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 3)
    - PAC mailings September 21, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Northern Virginia-ACLU Members (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Women's Campaign Fund-application (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Labor PAC Mailing (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 7)
    - AIPAC attendees 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Federal Election Commission (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Federal Election Commission April-June 30, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Federal Election Commission July 1-September 30, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Federal Election Commission October 1-17, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Itemized Reciepts and Disbursements (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising Plan (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Finance-Federal Election Commission Campaign Chart June 30, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Finance Committee (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Harnett and Associates (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 17)
    - "In-Kind" Contrbiutions (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Rick's Fundraising Plan (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Jonell's Notes (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Campaign Prospectus (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Possible Fundraising Events (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Finance-Matt Reese and Associates invoices (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Fundraising Record Form (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Contributors [computer printout] (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Contributions August 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Contributions September 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Contributions October 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Contributions (through) August 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Contribution Cards [Name, address, amount] (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Well Wishers (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Contributions-Copies of Checks (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Individualized Thanks Copies (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Over $200 Contributors List (as of) August 1 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Contributions (as of) October 2 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Contributors-First F.E.C. Report March 31, 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Harrison Contributors $100-$200 only (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Harrison for U.S. Senate Contributions 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Lists for Thank Yous (sent in) August, September, October, November 1984 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Warner-Sponsored Bills (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Thanks Sent-Lists (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Birthday Thank Yous (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 3)
    - California Thanks Sent (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Contributors (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Contributor List [computer prinout] (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Contribution Cards (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions I (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions II (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions III (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions IV (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions V (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions VI (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions VII (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Checks and Contributions VIII (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Field Plan 1984 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Congressional District 1 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Volunteers Congressional District 1 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Congressional District [blue folder] (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Election Day Workers-Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Election Day Workers-Norfolk (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Beach Office Opening (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Tidewater Office (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Congressional District 2 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk Precinct Finder (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Congressional District 2 Zip Codes (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Richmond Zip Code Directory (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Congressional District 3 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Congressional District 4 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Congressional District 5 I (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Congressional District 5 II (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Congressional District 6 I (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Congressional District 6 II (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Congressional District 7 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Congressional District 8 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Congressional District 9 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Congressional District 10 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Master List of Edythe Harrison Volunteers (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax-Data Base (FCDC) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Northern Virginia Office Schedule and Materials (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Congressional District? (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
    - State Central Committee (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Leaders (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Labels for Volunteers (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Volunteers-Original (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Field Manual (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Field Materials (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Literature Distribution (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Districts-Maps (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Targeting Information (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Election Day-Rules and Regulations November 6, 1984 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Precinct Captain Work Sheets (for election day) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Desk Operations (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 19)
    - GOTV Plan (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Vrginia Poll September 1, 1984 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Sample Birthday Party Kit (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 22)
    - City Council Members (whole state) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Statewide Lists (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Commission on the Status of Women (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Displaced Homemaker Program (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Women General Assembly Members (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Office (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Women Constitutional Officers (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Women Contacts (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Registered Lobbyists 1983-84 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
    - List of Virginia Associations (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Colleges/Universities by Congressional District (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Governor's Commission to Increase Voter Registration (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Senior Citizen's Network (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Women's Groups (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 14)
    - NARFE (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Black and Hispanic Voters (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Hispanic (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Labor (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Black Community (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Organization for Rehablitation Through Training Men's List 1982 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Requests Filled (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Birthday Wishes (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Volunteers Congressional Districts 1, 2, 3, 4 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Volunteers Congressional Districts 5, 6, 7, 9 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Volunteers Congressional Districts 8, 10 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Volunteers-names now on 4 x 6 Cards (after) July 15, 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Leaders-Names Have Been Added to Leader List 1, 2, 3, 4 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Message Survey Response July & August 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Election Maps 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
    - League of Women Voters Debate September 9, 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Capitol Correspondents Debate (PBS-TV) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Debate: Capital Correspondents (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Debate: Questions from Warner (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Richmond Chamber Debate (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee Debate Prep Memo (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Briefings-Debate Prep July 12, 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Press Release: Pre-Convention senate Campaign (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Post-Convention Press Releases (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Press Release: Arms Control October 2, 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Harrison Campaign Activity (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Press Release:American Cancer Society Event at King's Dominion (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Press Release: Civil Rights Act (of) 1984 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Press Conference "Give the Money Back"-Richmond October 17, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Defense PAC Money to Warner (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Press Release: "Tainted Money" October 24, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
    - "Tainted Money" Fact Sheet (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Press Statement: Warner's Connection to Defense Contractors October 31, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Press Release: Debate Weekly Schedule (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Press Statement: Joint Appearances October 15, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Press Release: Hampton Roads Harbor October 24, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Warner-Helms (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Press Release: Marathon (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Press Statement: Military Service Requirement for Senate? (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Press Release: Norfolk Naval Base September 14, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Letter to Editor: Primary (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Press Release: Richmond Headquarters Opening September 17, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Nuts and Bolts: Spare Parts Catalog (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Press Release: Tapella Resigns June 20, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Press Conference: Women's Rights and Warner August 8, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Press Release: Women's Rights Richmond October 26, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases: Schedules (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Election Press Releases January-August 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Election Press Releases September-November 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Morrison Letter-Editorial Page Editor October 14, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 22)
    - WINC Editorial and Response (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Stoddart Meeting September 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch Transcript of Interview August 30, 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Washington Post Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Nuts and Bolts-Spare Parts Catalog (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Sample Press Packet-Democratic National Convention (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Sample Press Packet July 1984 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 29)